animeseed.com 2008-06-13

# Privacy Policy | AnimeSeed.Com

## [Privacy Policy](http://animeseed.com/index.php/privacy-policy "Privacy Policy")

Anime Seed knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, we appreciate your trust. We would like you to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your personal information. The following information describe types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit Anime Seed, and how we safeguard your information.

### Log Files

As with most other websites, Anime Seed collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocal) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you the features you enabled from previous visit, or the ability to login to some of our member only system or forum.

We also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google AdSense, Yahoo Publisher Network, etc) information including your ISP, IP address, the browser you used to visit our site, and in certain cases, whether you have certain browser feature installed or activated. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain advertisement based on specific sites visited.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs that you use to manage your internet security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could result in the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

### Contact Information

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff. Please contact us using the contacts listed in our [contact page](http://animeseed.com/index.php/contact-page).
